let savollar4 = [
    {
      numb: 1,
      question: "to bloom",
      answer: "B. gullamoq",
      options: [
        "A. qurimoq",
        "B. gullamoq",
        "C. so'lib qolmoq",
        "D. o'smoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 2,
      question: "compact",
      answer: "C. ixcham",
      options: [
        "A. keng",
        "B. tartibsiz",
        "C. ixcham",
        "D. katta"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 3,
      question: "curl",
      answer: "D. jingalak",
      options: [
        "A. tugun",
        "B. ip",
        "C. tasma",
        "D. jingalak"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 4,
      question: "to decay",
      answer: "A. chirimoq",
      options: [
        "A. chirimoq",
        "B. tiklanmoq",
        "C. o'smoq",
        "D. yaxshilanmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: "dessert",
      answer: "B. shirinlik",
      options: [
        "A. sho'rva",
        "B. shirinlik",
        "C. asosiy taom",
        "D. gazak"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 6,
      question: "to dip",
      answer: "D. botirmoq",
      options: [
        "A. quritmoq",
        "B. olib tashlamoq",
        "C. yuvmoq",
        "D. botirmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 7,
      question: "distant",
      answer: "C. uzoq",
      options: [
        "A. yaqin",
        "B. ko'rinadigan",
        "C. uzoq",
        "D. tanish"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 8,
      question: "eclipse",
      answer: "A. oy tutilishi",
      options: [
        "A. oy tutilishi",
        "B. soya",
        "C. quyosh chiqishi",
        "D. qorong'ilik"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 9,
      question: "fairy",
      answer: "B. paricha",
      options: [
        "A. arvoh",
        "B. paricha",
        "C. mitti odam",
        "D. ajdaho"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 10,
      question: "grace",
      answer: "A. noziklik",
      options: [
        "A. noziklik",
        "B. qattiqlik",
        "C. shoshilish",
        "D. harakatsizlik"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 11,
      question: "leisure",
      answer: "B. bo'sh vaqt",
      options: [
        "A. ish vaqti",
        "B. bo'sh vaqt",
        "C. majburiyat",
        "D. kechikish"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 12,
      question: "mankind",
      answer: "A. insoniyat",
      options: [
        "A. insoniyat",
        "B. hayvonot",
        "C. tabiat",
        "D. xalq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 13,
      question: "passion",
      answer: "C. kuchli ehtiros",
      options: [
        "A. xotirjamlik",
        "B. befarqlik",
        "C. kuchli ehtiros",
        "D. gumon"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 14,
      question: "pillow",
      answer: "D. yostiq",
      options: [
        "A. adyol",
        "B. choyshab",
        "C. to'shak",
        "D. yostiq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 15,
      question: "pulse",
      answer: "A. puls",
      options: [
        "A. puls",
        "B. qon",
        "C. yurak",
        "D. ritm"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 16,
      question: "to refresh",
      answer: "B. jonlantirmoq",
      options: [
        "A. charchatmoq",
        "B. jonlantirmoq",
        "C. quritmoq",
        "D. susaytirmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 17,
      question: "to sneeze",
      answer: "A. aksirmoq",
      options: [
        "A. aksirmoq",
        "B. yo'tirmoq",
        "C. hushtak chalmoq",
        "D. yig'lamoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 18,
      question: "spice",
      answer: "B. ziravor",
      options: [
        "A. shakar",
        "B. ziravor",
        "C. tuz",
        "D. yog'"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 19,
      question: "to whistle",
      answer: "D. hushtak chalmoq",
      options: [
        "A. qo'shiq aytmoq",
        "B. chaqirmoq",
        "C. shivirlab aytmoq",
        "D. hushtak chalmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 20,
      question: "wool",
      answer: "C. jun",
      options: [
        "A. ipak",
        "B. paxta",
        "C. jun",
        "D. charm"
      ]
    }
  ];
  
  export default savollar4;